<resources>
    <string name="rules_text">
        Welcome to Minesweeper!\n
    When you play, you are met with a grid. Some of these have a mine hidden underneath!\n
        At the bottom left, you have your timer, which tracks how long you take, and a mines remaining
        window, which shows how many untracked mines remain.\n
        All tiles start in the UNKNOWN state. A tile may have 1 or 0 mines underneath it.\n\n
    Your first click will expose your first tile, which is guaranteed to be SAFE. Try it now!\n
        None of its neighbors will have mines.\n
        Because it has no mines in its 3x3 neighborhood, it will reveal all tiles around it.\n
        ---------------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\n
        ---------------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ 0\ |\ 0\ |\ 0\ |\ \ \ \ |\n
        ---------------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ 0\ |\ X\ |\ 0\ |\ \ \ \ |\n
        ---------------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ 0\ |\ 0\ |\ 0\ |\ \ \ \ |\n
        ---------------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\n
        ---------------------\n
        e.g., All tiles marked \"0\" are in the neighborhood of tile \"X\"\n\n
        If your tile is connected to other tiles with no adjacent mines, it will chain and reveal
        the tiles around those tiles!\n\n
        Some SAFE tiles have number on them. These numbers show how many mines are in its neighborhood.\n
        At the bottom right, you have a cursor selector. Its default is the FLAG cursor.\n
        With the flag cursor, you can mark tiles you think are suspicious. This will reduce the
        untracked mine counter.\n
        Do you see a tile that has a \"1\" and only 1 UNKNOWN tile in its neighborhood?\n\n
        -------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\n
        -------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\ 1\ |\n
        -------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ 2\ |\ 1\ |\n
        -------------\n
        e.g., The bottom right tile only has 1 UNKNOWN tile in its neighborhood - the middle tile, and expects 1 mine in its neighborhood.\n\n
        If you see this, it means that the UNKNOWN tile definitely has a mine under it.\n
        With the FLAG cursor selected, tag the UNKNOWN tile as FLAGGED.\n
        If a nearby tile also has a \"1\", and one of its UNKNOWN tiles is flagged, that means that
        all the other UNKNOWN tiles in its neighborhood are now safe!\n\n
        -------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ S\ |\ S\ |\n
        -------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ F\ |\ 1\ |\n
        -------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ 2\ |\ 1\ |\n
        -------------\n
        e.g., the middle right tile expects 1 mine in its neighborhood, and that\'s confirmed to be
        in the middle tile due to the bottom right tile. Therefore, the top middle and top right tiles are safe!\n\n
        With the DIG cursor, you can directly expose an UNKNOWN tile you think is safe. If you dig a tile with a mine, it
        will explode, and you will lose!\n
        If you have a UNKNOWN tile you think is safe, try clicking on it with the DIG cursor!\n\n
        -------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ S\ |\ 1\ |\n
        -------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ F\ |\ 1\ |\n
        -------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ 2\ |\ 1\ |\n
        -------------\n
        I clicked on the top right and exposed the safe tile. But you don\'t have to click on each tile
        individually. Whether you\'re in FLAG or DIG mode, you can click on a tile that is already SAFE.\n
        If that tile\'s number of expected neighbor mines matches the number of flags in its neighborhood,
        it will DIG all the unflagged tiles in its neighborhood. What a deal!\n\n
        -------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\n
        -------------\n
        |\ \ \ \ |\ 1\ |\ \ \ \ |\n
        -------------\n
        |\ F\ |\ \ \ \ |\ \ \ \ |\n
        -------------\n
        e.g., if I click on the middle tile, because it is expecting 1 mine and has 1 flag, DIG will
        occur on every tile in its neighborhood other than the flagged tile and the safe tile.\n\n
        Be careful though! If you flag erroneously, and the mine isn\'t under the tile you flagged,
        it will blow up and you will lose the game!
    </string>
    <!--    TITLE TEXT        -->
    <string name="app_name">Minesweeper</string>
    <string name="title">Minesweeper</string>
    <string name="menu_title">Menu</string>
    <string name="rules_title">Rules</string>
    <string name="scores_title">Scores</string>
    <string name="play_title">Play</string>

    <string name="play_again_btn_text">Play Again</string>

    <!--    ENDSCREEN STRINGS   -->
    <string name="win_message">Winner!</string>
    <string name="lose_message">Good Try!</string>

    <!--    GAMEPLAY STRINGS        -->
    <string name="difficulty_easy_btn_text">EASY</string>
    <string name="difficulty_medium_btn_text">MEDIUM</string>

    <!--    SCORE STRINGS   -->
    <string name="reset_btn_text">reset</string>
    <string name="placeholder_name">Jimothy</string>
    <string name="placeholder_time">15:33.2</string>
    <string name="placeholder_mines_count">10</string>

    <!--    SCORE DISPLAY STRINGS -->
    <string name="last_score_label">Your last score:</string>
    <string name="user_top_score_label">Your shortest time was:</string>
    <string name="total_top_score_label">Shortest total time:</string>
    <string name="new_personal_best_message">You have a new personal best!</string>
    <string name="gold_label">Gold Medallist</string>
    <string name="silver_label">Silver Medallist</string>
    <string name="bronze_label">Bronze Medallist</string>
    <string name="new_lead_message">You are in the top 3! Check the scores to see your rank.</string>

</resources>